[ ENGINE STARTS ]
♪ NOW , ON THE DAY I WAS BORN ♪
♪ THE NURSES ALL GATHERED ' ROUND ♪
♪ AND THEY GAZED IN WIDE WONDER ♪
♪ AT THE JOY THEY HAD FOUND ♪
♪ THE HEAD NURSE SPOKE UP ♪
♪ SAID , " LEAVE THIS ONE ALONE " ♪
♪ SHE COULD TELL RIGHT AWAY ♪
♪ THAT I WAS BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ B-B-B-B-B-BAD ♪
♪ I BROKE 1,000 HEARTS ♪
♪ BEFORE I MET YOU ♪
♪ I 'LL BREAK 1,000 MORE , BABY ♪
♪ BEFORE I AM THROUGH ♪
♪ I WANT TO BE YOURS , PRETTY BABY ♪
♪ YOURS , AND YOURS ALONE ♪
♪ I 'M HERE TO TELL YOU , HONEY ♪
♪ THAT I 'M BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ B-B-B-B-B-BAD ♪
♪ BAD TO THE BONE ♪ ♪
[ SCREAMS ]
♪ I 'M A-GONNA TELL YOU HOW IT 'S GONNA BE ♪
♪ BOP BOP OOH WOP BOP BOP ♪
♪ YOU GONNA GIVE YOUR LOVE TO ME ♪
♪ BOP BOP OOH WOP BOP BOP ♪ ♪
[ BELL RINGS ]
[ SONG CONTINUES , FAINT ]
♪ BOP BOP OOH WOP BOP BOP ♪
♪ MY LOVE IS BIGGER THAN A CADILLAC ♪
♪ I TRY TO SHOW YOU BUT YOU DRIVE ME BACK ♪
♪ BOP BOP OOH WOP BOP BOP ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE FOR ME HAS GOT TO BE REAL ♪
HOLY SHIT !
[ HONK HONK HONK ]
♪ LOVE IS REAL AND NOT FADE AWAY ♪
♪ I SAID LOVE IS REAL AND NOT FADE AWAY ♪
[ HONK HONK HONK ]
COME ON , ARNIE .
[ HONK HONK ]
HE 'S COMING .
HE 'S CHANGING HIS SHIRT .
♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪ ♪
THAT 'S NOISE POLLUTION , WHAT YOU 'RE DOING .
YOU MIGHT AS WELL BE DUMPING TOXIC WASTE ON OUR LAWN .
HEY , DENNIS . I 'LL BE RIGHT THERE .
JUST LEAVE IT . IT 'S OKAY . GO ON .
UH , ARNIE , YOUR LUNCH !
AND TRY AND KEEP IT COLD . THERE 'S YOGURT IN THERE .
RIGHT .
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
SLOW DOWN !
ARE YOU GUYS HAVING A WAR ?
SHE 'S PISSED OFF 'CAUSE I 'M TAKING SHOP .
LIKE IT EMBARRASSES HER OR SOMETHING . MY DAD TOO .
IT WON 'T EMBARRASS ' EM WHEN THEIR STUPID VOLVO BREAKS DOWN
AND YOU FIX IT FOR FREE .
LAST NIGHT , WE 'RE PLAYING SCRABBLE ,
IT 'S NECK AND NECK BETWEEN ME AND HER .
WE BLEW MY DAD AWAY EARLY .
SO RIGHT AT THE END , I HAD THIS CHOICE OF USING " RATIO "
FOR FIVE LOUSY POINTS ,
OR ...
OR WHAT , ARNIE ?
" FELLATIO " ON A TRIPLE WORD SCORE FOR 24 POINTS AND THE GAME .
WHAT 'D SHE DO ?
SHE WOULDN 'T LET ME HAVE IT . SHE WON BY SEVEN POINTS .
SHE SAID OBSCENITY 'S NOT ALLOWED IN SCRABBLE .
I LOOKED IT UP . IT 'S IN THE DICTIONARY .
YOU JERK , ARNIE .
JESUS .
YOU KNOW , ARNIE , I WAS THINKING ...
UH-OH .
NO , SERIOUSLY .
NOW THAT WE 'RE GOING TO BE SENIORS ,
I FIGURED IT 'S ABOUT TIME WE GOT YOU LAID .
LIKE THIS YEAR .
YOU NEED A GIRL TO GET LAID .
WHAT ABOUT GAIL JUSTIN ?
OH , GAIL JUST IN CASE ? I DON 'T LIKE HER MUSTACHE .
WHAT DO YOU CARE IF YOU GET A LITTLE HAIR IN YOUR MOUTH ?
OKAY . HOW ABOUT SALLY HAYES ? SHE 'S CUTE .
SHE 'S A SOPHOMORE !
SHE 'S A WALKING SPERM BANK . I KNOW . COME ON .
I DON 'T HAVE THE MINIMUM DEPOSIT TO OPEN AN ACCOUNT .
ARE YOU KIDDING ? YOU CARRY YOUR LIFE SAVINGS BETWEEN YOUR LEGS .
COME ON , ARNIE .
I THINK MAYBE I 'LL JUST BEAT OFF .
ARE YOU PLAYING FOOTBALL THIS YEAR ?
SOMEBODY 'S GOTTA PICK IT UP WHEN YOU FUMBLE .
HA HA . HOW 'S YOUR GIMPY KNEE ?
BETTER . COACH WANTS ME TO PRACTICE .
WELL , IT 'S ABOUT TIME . I 'VE BEEN EATING DIRT WITH YOUR NAME ON IT
FOR THE PAST THREE WEEKS .
HI , DENNIS .
OH , HEY , ROSEANNE .
HOW YOU DOING ?
I 'M OKAY . THEY GONNA LET YOU PLAY FOOTBALL THIS YEAR ?
YEAH . DOC SAYS I 'M AS GOOD AS NEW .
I GUESS I 'LL BE SEEING YOU OUT THERE .
I HOPE SO .
WELL ... T.T.F.N.
YEAH . TA-TA FOR NOW .
I WOULDN 'T PUT THAT IN MY MOUTH .
YOU DON 'T KNOW WHERE IT 'S BEEN .
WE KNOW WHERE IT HASN 'T BEEN . HASN 'T BEEN WITH YOU .
HAVING TROUBLE WITH YOUR LOCKER ?
NO .
SEEN THE NEW GIRL ?
I JUST GOT HERE .
DENNIS , I 'M IN LOVE . SHE 'S PERFECT , AND YOU KNOW HOW FUSSY I AM .
I NEVER NOTICED YOU WERE FUSSY .
DROP DEAD , CUNNINGHAM .
WHAT 'S HER NAME ?
I DON 'T KNOW . SHE 'S IN THE OFFICE .
SHE LOOKS SMART , BUT SHE 'S GOT THE BODY OF A SLUT .
OH , SHIT .
HERE SHE COMES .
GIVE ME SOMETHING FOR MY LAP .
WE HAVE ONE HECK OF A MARCHING BAND .
WENT TO THE ROSE PARADE LAST YEAR .
NOT A BAD WAY TO MEET BOYS .
I WOULD LIKE TO GET INVOLVED WITH THE YEARBOOK .
WE HAVE A TERRIFIC YEARBOOK STAFF .
THEY WON A PRIZE LAST YEAR .
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT ADMITTING RED CHINA INTO THE U. N ?
I THINK WE ALREADY DID THAT .
DO YOU THINK IT WAS A GOOD IDEA ?
SHE SMILED AT ME .
I WANT TO HAVE DEEP , MEANINGFUL SEX WITH HER .
GO GET HER , BEMIS .
THINK I SHOULD ?
YOU 'VE GOT NOTHING TO LOSE BUT YOUR VIRGINITY .
DENNIS , CAN YOU GIVE ME A HAND ?
I CAN 'T ...
YEAH .
HE DOESN 'T HAVE A CHANCE .
OH , I DON 'T THINK SO EITHER .
SHE 'S MUCH TOO CLASSY FOR HIM .
THERE YOU GO .
WHAT DID YOU DO ?
LUCKY . SEE YOU AT LUNCH .
OKAY .
HEY , CHARLIE . HAVE YOU SEEN ARNIE ?
YEAH . HE 'S STILL IN THE SHOP .
WHAT 'S THE MATTER ?
BUDDY REPPERTON HAS HIS LUNCH .
BUDDY REPPERTON .
HI , DENNl —
GO ON , PIZZA FACE .
DO YOU WANT IT ? COME GET IT !
IF IT 'S YOURS , WHY DOESN 'T IT HAVE YOUR NAME ON HERE ?
" ARNIE CUNTINGHAM . "
WHY DOESN 'T IT SAY CUNTINGHAM ?
JUST TAKE IT , ARNIE , AND LET 'S GO EAT .
YEAH . THAT 'S ALL YOU GOT TO DO . COME ON .
COME ON .
THAT 'S FUNNY , BUDDY , REAL FUNNY .
GO GET MR. CASEY .
COME ON . WANT TO GO FOR IT ?
PUT THE KNIFE DOWN AND I WILL .
PUT DOWN THE KNIFE , REPPERTON .
YOU WANT TO MAKE ME ?
YOU GOT A KNIFE AND HE DOESN 'T .
IN MY BOOK , THAT MAKES YOU A CHICKENSHIT .
YEAH . THAT 'S CHICKENSHIT .
OH , YEAH ? PUT IT DOWN , BUDDY .
PUT DOWN THE KNIFE .
COME ON , BUDDY , JUST PUT DOWN THE KNIFE , OKAY ?
JUST PUT IT DOWN .
GET HIM , MAN !
COME ON , STICK HIM .
STICK HIM , BUDDY .
HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT , DICKFACE ?
ALL RIGHT , BREAK IT UP !
YOU KIDS TAKE A WALK . GET LOST .
NOT YOU , MOOCHIE .
I AIN 'T BEEN DOING NOTHING .
YOU ALL RIGHT , DENNIS ?
YEAH , I 'M OKAY .
I 'M OKAY .
REAL CUTE . THREE ON ONE .
THEY STARTED IT .
[ ARNIE ] THAT 'S NOT TRUE .
SHUT UP , CUNTFACE !
SHUT YOUR MOUTH !
I DON 'T HAVE TO LISTEN TO GARBAGE LIKE THAT COMING FROM YOU , BUDDY !
WHAT WERE YOU SAYING , ARNIE ?
REPPERTON 'S GOT A KNIFE .
YOU FUCKING LIAR !
IT 'S A SWITCHBLADE .
THAT 'S BULLSHIT , MR. CASEY .
HE 'S LYING . I SWEAR .
CUNNINGHAM , DID REPPERTON HERE PULL A KNIFE ON YOU ?
YEAH .
EMPTY YOUR POCKETS , BUDDY .
FUCK I WILL .
YOU CAN 'T MAKE ME .
YOU MEAN I DON 'T HAVE THE AUTHORITY , YOU 'RE WRONG .
I CAN TURN OUT YOUR POCKETS —
TRY IT , AND I 'LL KNOCK YOU THROUGH THE WALL !
YOU TWO GO UP TO THE OFFICE .
STAY THERE . YOU 'VE GOT ENOUGH TROUBLE .
IF YOU DON 'T EMPTY YOUR POCKETS ,
I 'LL CALL THE COPS .
GO TO THE OFFICE , BUDDY .
I 'LL FIX YOU !
YOU 'LL WISH YOU WERE NEVER FUCKING BORN !
ALL IN ALL ,
IT WASN 'T A BAD FIRST DAY .
THINK REPPERTON WILL TRY TO GET EVEN ?
NO , HE 'S A DOUCHE BAG .
HE 'LL FIND SOMEBODY ELSE TO PICK ON .
THEY KICKED HIM OUT .
GOOD . THEY KICK MOOCHIE OUT ?
PROBATION .
THOSE ASSHOLES .
STOP THE CAR ! GO BACK ! GO BACK .
WHAT 'S THE MATTER ?
I WANT TO LOOK AT HER ! ALL RIGHT , ARNIE .
JUST GO BACK !
JESUS CHRIST .
WHAT IS IT ?
DO YOU KNOW SOMEONE WHO LIVES HERE ?
WHAT ?
JESUS .
BE CAREFUL , DENNIS .
THIS IS A PIECE OF SHIT , ARNIE .
SHE COULD BE FIXED UP .
SHE COULD . YEAH .
OH , SHE COULD BE REALLY TOUGH .
FORGET IT , ARNIE .
THIS BABY 'S GOT 93,000 MILES ON IT .
PROBABLY 193 .
I DON 'T CARE .
I BET IT WON 'T EVEN START .
SHE 'LL START .
YOU NEED THESE .
HOW MUCH DO YOU WANT FOR HER ?
WHATEVER IT IS , IT 'S NOT ENOUGH .
JESUS , ARNIE .
YOU EVER OWNED A CAR BEFORE ?
YEAH , HE OWNS A MUSTAN —
NO . I JUST GOT MY LICENSE .
NAME 'S GEORGE LeBAY .
ARNIE CUNNINGHAM .
WHAT ARE YOU ASKING ?
START HER UP .
REALLY ?
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
HER NAME 'S CHRISTINE .
I LIKE THAT .
WE GOT TO GO .
MY ASSHOLE BROTHER BOUGHT HER IN ' 57 .
YOU GOT YOUR NEW MODEL YEAR IN SEPTEMBER .
BRAND NEW , SHE WAS .
SHE HAD THE SMELL OF A BRAND NEW CAR .
THAT 'S JUST ABOUT THE FINEST SMELL IN THE WORLD ,
EXCEPT MAYBE FOR PUSSY .
WHEN HE GOT HER , SHE HAD SIX MILES ON THE ODOMETER .
GODDAMN ROLAND WENT THROUGH HELL AND BACK WITH CHRISTINE .
IF YOUR BROTHER LOVES THIS CAR SO MUCH ,
WHY IS HE SELLING IT ?
'CAUSE HE 'S STONE COLD DEAD .
DIED SIX WEEKS AGO .
SO , MR. LeBAY ...
HOW MUCH DO YOU WANT FOR HER ?
I 'VE BEEN ASKING 300 .
I 'LL MAKE IT 250 FOR YOU .
250 ?
THIS ISN 'T WORTH $ 50 .
THE MONEY 'S NOT IMPORTANT .
THERE 'LL BE NO BRINGING HER BACK .
I 'M SELLING THIS SHITHOLE AND BUYING A CONDO .
YOU GOT A DEAL .
I 'LL GET THE PINK SLIP .
ARNIE , STOP AND THINK ABOUT THIS .
WHERE ARE YOU GETTING THE MONEY ?
I 'VE BEEN SAVING .
YEAH , FOR COLLEGE . EASY FOR YOU TO SAY . YOU ALREADY HAVE A CAR .
HE 'S SCREWING YOU .
YOU COULD GET A DECENT CAR FOR THAT MUCH MONEY .
CHRISTINE IS DECENT .
THE GUY 'S WEIRD , ARNIE .
HE 'S FUCKING WEIRD .
SO , UM , THAT WAS 300 ?
YEAH , THAT 'S IT .
[ DENNIS ] YOU SAID 250 .
250 WOULD DO IT .
LET 'S JUST COME BACK TOMORROW .
DO YOU REALIZE SHE 'S 20 YEARS OLD ?
I MEAN , THAT MAKES HER OFFICIALLY AN ANTIQUE .
GREAT . DARNELL 'S JUNKYARD IS FULL OF OFFICIAL ANTIQUES .
I 'M BUYING HER .
I DON 'T CARE WHAT YOU SAY .
IT 'S YOUR FUNERAL , MAN .
WOULD YOU GIVE ARNIE A BREAK ?
HE DOESN 'T KNOW WHAT HE 'S DOING .
YOU DON 'T KNOW HALF AS MUCH AS YOU THINK YOU DO ,
SHITTER .
YOU DID WHAT ?
SHE 'S OUTSIDE .
YOU 'RE KIDDING , RIGHT ?
YOU CAN 'T BUY A CAR .
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
YOU 'RE 17 YEARS OLD .
OH , BOY .
ACTUALLY , YOU 'RE WRONG .
I COULDN 'T FINANCE IT , BUT BUYING IT FOR CASH IS NO PROBLEM .
REGISTERING A CAR AT 17 IS SOMETHING ELSE ,
AND FOR THAT I NEED YOUR PERMISSION .
YOU KNOW HOW WE DO THINGS .
YOU COULD 'VE CONSULTED WITH US .
I 'VE CONSULTED WITH YOU
ABOUT EVERYTHING I 'VE EVER DONE .
EVERYTHING IN THIS HOUSE IS A COMMITTEE MEETING , AND IF IT 'S SOMETHING I WANT ,
I 'M OUTVOTED TWO TO ONE !
THIS IS NO COMMITTEE MEETING . THE CAR 'S MINE ! THAT 'S IT !
IT MOST CERTAINLY IS NOT IT !
HOW COULD YOU HAVE LET HIM DO THIS ?
I DIDN 'T LET HIM .
HE WANTED THE CAR AND HE BOUGHT IT .
I TRIED TO TALK HIM OUT OF IT .
MMM . I DOUBT YOU TRIED VERY HARD .
YEAH , WELL , I 'M GOING HOME .
I THINK YOU SHOULD .
THAT 'S IT . I 'M GETTING THE FUCK OUT OF HERE .
WHAT DID YOU SAY ?
YOU WANTED ME IN COLLEGE COURSES ? I 'M THERE .
YOU WANTED ME IN CHESS CLUB INSTEAD OF THE BAND ? OKAY , I 'M THERE TOO .
I 'VE MANAGED TO GET THROUGH 17 YEARS
WITHOUT EMBARRASSING YOU IN FRONT OF YOUR BRIDGE CLUB
OR LANDING IN JAIL !
I 'M GOING TO HAVE THIS ONE THING !
YOU ARE NOT KEEPING ANY CAR AT THIS HOUSE .
FINE !
THANKS FOR THE MILK .
WHAT 'S THE PROBLEM ?
COULD YOU HONK YOUR HORN FOR ME ?
CHRISTINE 'S DOESN 'T SEEM TO WORK .
SURE .
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ HONK HONK HONK ]
STALL 20 .
STALL 20 !
GET IT OVER THERE AND SHUT IT OFF
BEFORE WE ALL CHOKE TO DEATH .
YOU SOLD HIM THAT PIECE OF SHIT ,
YOU OUGHTA BE ASHAMED OF YOURSELF .
I DIDN 'T SELL IT TO HIM .
I TRIED TO TALK HIM OUT OF IT .
YOU SHOULD HAVE TRIED HARDER .
I KNEW A GUY WHO HAD A CAR LIKE THAT ONCE .
FUCKIN ' BASTARD KILLED HIMSELF IN IT .
SON OF A BITCH WAS SO MEAN ,
YOU COULD HAVE POURED BOILING WATER DOWN HIS THROAT ,
HE WOULD HAVE PISSED ICE CUBES .
THAT 'S THE LAST TIME
YOU RUN THAT MECHANICAL ASSHOLE IN HERE
WITHOUT AN EXHAUST HOSE .
DO IT ONCE , AND YOU 'RE OUT .
YOU UNDERSTAND ?
YES .
I 'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING ELSE .
I DON 'T TAKE ANY SHIT FROM YOU KIDS .
THIS PLACE IS FOR WORKING STIFFS GOTTA KEEP THEIR CARS RUNNING
SO THEY CAN PUT BREAD ON THE TABLE .
IT 'S NOT FOR SNOT-NOSED KIDS
WHO WANT TO GO DRAGGING .
I DON 'T ALLOW NO SMOKING HERE NEITHER .
YOU WANT A BUTT , YOU GO OUT IN THE JUNKYARD .
I DON 'T SMOKE . DON 'T INTERRUPT ME , PUNK .
DON 'T INTERRUPT ME . DON 'T GET SMART .
UH , SIR ? WHAT ?
THOSE MEN OVER THERE ARE SMOKING .
BETTER TELL THEM TO STOP .
YOU TRYING TO HELP YOUR BUDDY OUT OF HERE ?
NO .
THEN SHUT YOUR PIE HOLE .
I KNOW A CREEP WHEN I SEE ONE .
I 'M LOOKING AT ONE RIGHT NOW .
YOU 'RE ON PROBATION .
SCREW AROUND WITH ME ONE TIME —
I DON 'T CARE HOW MUCH MONEY YOU 'VE PAID —
I 'LL THROW YOU OUT ON YOUR ASS !
YOU GOT IT ? HUH ?
YES , SIR .
GOOD .
NOW GET THE HELL OUT . WE 'RE CLOSED .
YOU GOING TO BE OKAY ?
YEAH . I 'M OKAY .
YOU SHOULD FIND YOURSELF ANOTHER CHARITY
BESIDES ME AND CHRISTINE .
WHAT IS IT ABOUT THAT CAR ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
MAYBE IT 'S JUST THAT FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE ,
I 'VE FOUND SOMETHING UGLIER THAN ME .
AND I KNOW I CAN FIX HER UP .
YOU 'RE NOT UGLY , ARNIE .
I KNOW WHAT I AM .
QUEER , MAYBE , BUT NOT UGLY .
FUCK YOU .
ARNOLD !
BUG OUT , DENNIS . YOU DON 'T NEED THIS SHIT .
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN ?
YOU HAD US WORRIED SICK !
YOU DON 'T UP AND DRIVE OFF WHENEVER YOU —
[ RADIO ] ♪ AS I WALK ALONG ♪
♪ I WONDER ♪
♪ WHAT WENT WRONG ♪
♪ WITH OUR LOVE ♪
♪ A LOVE THAT WAS SO STRONG ... ♪ ♪
HE 'S DONE ALL THIS SHIT IN THREE WEEKS .
LOOK HOW COCK-EYED HE WORKS .
HE 'S GOT BRAND-NEW WINDSHIELD WIPERS
FOR A BUSTED WINDSHIELD .
WELL , THE BOY DOES HAVE GOOD HANDS .
GOOD HANDS .
BAD TASTE IN CARS .
YOU KNOW , PAPA ,
YOU CAN 'T POLISH A TURD .
WHEN I SAID YOU COULD SCROUNGE THROUGH THAT SHIT PILE OUT BACK ,
I DIDN 'T MEAN YOU COULD BUILD
YOUR WHOLE FUCKIN ' CAR WITH MY STUFF .
WHAT DO YOU CARE ?
YOU 'RE NOT DOING ANYTHING WITH IT .
HEY ! DON 'T THINK YOU GOT THE GOLD KEY TO THE CRAPPER .
NOBODY TAKES ADVANTAGE OF ME , UNDERSTAND ?
YEAH .
IF IT WASN 'T FOR ME , IT 'D COST YOU A WHOLE SHITPILE OF DOUGH
TO PUT THIS HEAP TOGETHER .
I KNOW .
LOOK .
I KNOW YOU AIN 'T GOT MONEY FALLING OUT OF YOUR ASSHOLE .
IF YOU DID , YOU WOULDN 'T BE HERE .
MAYBE WE COULD WORK OUT A DEAL .
YOU , UH ...
PICK UP AROUND THE PLACE .
DO A FEW LUBES ,
PUT THE TOILET PAPER ON THE LITTLE SPOOLS ,
SHIT LIKE THAT .
DO THAT AND YOU CAN , UH ...
YOU CAN RAID MY JUNK PILE FOR WHATEVER YOU WANT .
I MIGHT EVEN THROW IN A FEW BUCKS .
I 'LL HAVE TO THINK ABOUT IT .
DON 'T THINK ABOUT IT TOO LONG .
I 'LL THROW YOU OUT ON YOUR ASS .
♪ FOREVER , MY DARLING ♪
♪ MY LOVE WILL BE TRUE ♪
♪ ALWAYS AND FOREVER ♪
♪ I 'LL LOVE JUST YOU ♪
♪ JUST PROMISE ME , DARLING ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE IN RETURN ♪
♪ MAKE THIS FIRE IN MY SOUL , DEAR ♪
♪ FOREVER BURN ♪
♪ MY HEART 'S AT YOUR COMMAND , DEAR ... ♪ ♪
I 'LL BET YOU A DOLLAR SHE SAYS NO .
JUST ' CAUSE SHE SHOT YOU DOWN ?
SHE SAYS NO TO EVERYBODY .
LOOK WHAT SHE 'S DOING TO THAT PENCIL .
I WISH I WAS AN ERASER .
GO ON , STUDLY .
ASK HER OUT .
MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS . JUST READ THE BOOK .
YEAH , COME ON , GUILDER .
JUST DON 'T TIP THE TABLE OVER .
OKAY .
WHAT ARE YOU READING ?
HISTORY .
OH .
IT 'S PRETTY BORING , HUH ?
YEAH .
DO YOU LIKE MUSIC ?
UH-HUH .
WHAT ABOUT DANCING ?
YES .
DO YOU THINK YOU MIGHT , UM ...
WANT TO GO DANCING WITH ME ...
MAYBE FRIDAY NIGHT AFTER THE GAME ?
I 'M SORRY . I CAN 'T .
WHY NOT ?
I HAVE A DATE .
MR. GILDER !
ARE YOU LOST ?
NO , MA 'AM .
WHY DON 'T YOU RETURN TO YOUR SEAT
AND GET BACK TO WORK .
YEAH .
[ FATHER ] ARNIE , STAY HERE . LET 'S TALK THIS OVER .
[ MOTHER ] THIS ISN 'T A HOTEL YOU DROP IN AND OUT OF .
[ ARNIE ] I DON 'T NEED THIS .
WHAT DO YOU NEED ?
I NEED TO LEAVE .
ARNIE , COME BACK HERE !
HEY , ARNIE .
OH , SHIT .
GREETINGS TO YOU , TOO .
HEY , MAN , NO GLASSES .
YOU 'RE LOOKING GOOD .
I CAN 'T MAKE IT .
I MEANT TO CALL YOU , BUT I FORGOT .
IS DENNIS GOING WITH YOU ?
ARE YOU GOING WITH HIM ?
UH ... AM I ?
NO . I GOTTA DO AN ERRAND FOR DARNELL .
NEED A RIDE ?
GOT HIS CAR . THANKS .
SORRY ABOUT THE MOVIE , BUT THIS IS WORK .
GOT TO GO .
DON 'T WORRY ABOUT IT .
DID YOU HAVE PLANS WITH DENNIS ?
YOU 'LL HAVE NO FRIENDS AT ALL
IF YOU TREAT PEOPLE THIS WAY .
GET OFF MY BACK !
YOU 'RE HIS BEST FRIEND .
WHAT 'S GOING ON ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
I HARDLY SEE HIM ANYMORE .
NEITHER DO WE .
EVER SINCE HE BOUGHT THAT CAR ,
HE 'S BEEN OBSESSED WITH IT .
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE ?
WHEN WE SIGNED THE REGISTRATION PAPERS AT TOWN HALL ,
THEY TOLD US
THE MAN WHO OWNED THAT CAR LAST
DIED IN IT OF CARBON MONOXIDE POISONING .
JESUS .
DOES ARNIE KNOW ABOUT THAT ?
ARNIE DOESN 'T KNOW ANYTHING ANYMORE .
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT ?
I KNOW ABOUT YOUR BROTHER .
I KNOW HE DIED CHOKING ON EXHAUST FUMES .
YOU DON 'T KNOW SHIT , KID .
MY BROTHER DIED 'CAUSE HE WANTED TO .
HE HAD A RUBBER HOSE FROM THE EXHAUST PIPE .
ARNIE WOULDN 'T BUY THAT CAR IF HE 'D KNOWN SOMEBODY DIED IN IT .
YOU DON 'T KNOW YOUR FRIEND VERY WELL .
HE HAD THE SAME LOOK MY BROTHER ALWAYS HAD .
PROBABLY THE ONLY THING MY BROTHER EVER LOVED WAS THAT CAR .
IF ANY SHITTER EVER CAME BETWEEN HIM AND CHRISTINE ,
IF THEY DID ,
WATCH OUT .
HIS 5-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER CHOKED TO DEATH IN IT .
HE WOULDN 'T GET RID OF HER .
HE RODE AROUND WITH THE RADIO BLARIN ' ,
NOT A CARE IN THE WORLD EXCEPT FOR CHRISTINE .
ONLY TIME I INTERFERED WAS WHEN RITA KILLED HERSELF .
WHO 'S RITA ?
HIS WIFE !
HE DIDN 'T CARE A RAT 'S ASS ABOUT HER .
SHE DIED THE SAME WAY HE DID .
I MADE HIM GET RID OF IT ...
FOR DECENCY , YOU KNOW ?
THE CAR CAME BACK LATER . THREE WEEKS LATER .
WHAT DO YOU MEAN , " CAME BACK " ?
♪ KEEP-A KNOCKIN ' , BUT YOU CAN 'T COME IN ♪
♪ COME BACK TOMORROW NIGHT AND TRY IT AGAIN ♪
♪ YOU SAID YOU LOVED ME , AND YOU CAN 'T COME IN ♪
♪ YOU SAID YOU LOVED ME — ♪
ALL RIGHT . 50 PASS ON GO .
READY ?
WANT ME TO GO DEEP ?
I 'LL GET YOU ON THE SECOND SHOT .
[ REPPERTON ] HEY , TRILONI .
IS THAT CUNTINGHAM 'S CAR ?
YEP .
I KNOW WHERE HE KEEPS IT .
DOWN ...
SET ...
GO !
YEA !
FUCKING SHIT !
GET A STRETCHER ! COME ON !
AHEM .
HEY , ARNIE .
5,000 DIRTY LIMERICKS .
OUGHT TO KEEP YOU BUSY FOR A WHILE .
THIS IS THE THIRD TIME I 'VE COME BY .
MUST BE DYNAMITE DRUGS . YOU 'RE ALWAYS ASLEEP .
DOESN 'T QUITE KILL THE PAIN .
ROCKBRIDGE HASN 'T WON A GAME SINCE YOU GOT HURT .
THAT MAKES YOU SOME KIND OF HERO , RIGHT ?
I WON 'T BE PLAYING FOOTBALL AGAIN .
EVER .
THE DOCTOR SAYS THAT ONE CENTIMETER MORE
AND I WOULD HAVE BEEN PARALYZED FROM THE WAIST DOWN .
SHITTERS DID SOME JOB ON YOU , HUH ?
SO WHAT 'S THIS ABOUT YOU AND LEIGH CABOT ?
WE LIKE EACH OTHER OKAY .
HO HO . LISTEN TO MR. COOL .
SHE 'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL IN THE SCHOOL .
WELL , IT 'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK .
I REALLY RESPECT HER MIND , AND ...
SHE LUSTS AFTER MY BODY ! WHAT CAN I SAY ?
FUCK YOU .
I SAW YOU GUYS AT THE GAME .
HOW 'D YOU GET THAT CAR FIXED UP LIKE THAT ?
OH , JUST PLAIN OLD-FASHIONED HARD WORK .
I STILL CAN 'T KEEP HER AT HOME .
MOM SAYS THE YARD LOOKS CROWDED .
I 'M SURPRISED THEY LET YOU REGISTER IT .
TOLD ' EM IF THEY DIDN 'T , I 'D DROP OUT OF SCHOOL .
ARE YOU SERIOUS ?
MM-HMM .
THEY JUST DON 'T WANT ME TO GROW UP .
THEN THEY 'D HAVE TO FACE GETTING OLD .
HAS IT EVER OCCURRED TO YOU ...
THAT PART OF BEING A PARENT ...
IS TRYING TO KILL YOUR KIDS ?
SEE YOU AROUND , PAL .
I 'M SORRY , ARNIE . I CAN 'T .
I 'M SORRY .
WHAT 'S THE MATTER ?
WHAT 'S WRONG ?
I CAN 'T .
HERE .
IN THAT CAR .
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ? WHY NOT ?
I HATE THAT CAR .
YOU CARE MORE ABOUT THAT CAR THAN YOU CARE ABOUT ME .
THAT 'S CRAZY , LEIGH .
WHO DO YOU SPEND MORE TIME WITH ?
LOOK , UH ...
YOU 'LL GONNA GET A COLD . COME ON .
COME ON .
GIRLS ARE SUPPOSED TO BE JEALOUS OF OTHER GIRLS , NOT CARS .
THIS CAR 'S A GIRL .
OH , PLEASE .
CUT IT OUT . DON 'T .
WHAT ? YOU DON 'T LIKE ME SLAPPING YOUR GIRL ?
IT SEEMS LIKE NOBODY LIKES MY CAR THESE DAYS .
OH , SHIT !
♪ YOU 'RE MINE ♪
♪ AND WE BELONG TOGETHER ♪
♪ YES , WE BELONG TOGETHER ♪
LEIGH !
♪ YES , IT BELONGS TO ONLY ME ... ♪
HEY !
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING ?
GET YOUR GODDAMN HANDS OFF HER !
WHOA , WHOA ! HEY !
YOU GONNA BE ALL RIGHT ?
YEAH , I 'M FINE NOW .
YOU SCARED THE HELL OUT OF ME .
THEN GET RID OF THAT CAR .
I 'M NOT GOING IN THAT CAR AGAIN .
WAIT A MINUTE . WAIT A MINUTE .
DON 'T YOU BLAME YOUR CHOKING ON CHRISTINE .
IT HAPPENED , ARNIE .
WHEN I CHOKED , SOMETHING HAPPENED .
THE RADIO CAME ON .
EVERYTHING GOT BRIGHT .
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING ?
I COULD 'VE DIED . YOU DIDN 'T HELP .
MY DOOR WAS LOCKED .
YOU DIDN 'T WANT THAT MAN TO HELP ME EITHER .
I THOUGHT HE WAS ATTACKING YOU .
I DIDN 'T KNOW HE WAS GONNA DO THE HEIMLICH MANEUVER .
- I COULD HAVE DONE THE HEIMLICH MANEUVER . - BUT YOU DIDN 'T .
THERE ARE OTHER THINGS .
THAT RADIO ?
IT ONLY GETS THOSE OLD SONGS .
SOMETIMES WHEN WE 'RE MAKING OUT ...
IT JUST STALLS .
AS IF THE CAR WERE JEALOUS , ARNIE .
THAT GODDAMN CAR !
I 'LL GET IT .
KNOW WHAT I THINK ?
I THINK YOU 'RE JUST SEXUALLY FRUSTRATED .
LOOK , LEIGH , UH ...
I 'M SORRY , OKAY ?
CAN I CALL YOU TOMORROW ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
COME ON .
COME ON , CHRISTINE .
COME ON , BABY , PLEASE .
IT 'S ALL RIGHT . EVERYTHING 'S THE SAME .
♪ ... I LOVE YOU LIKE I DO ♪
♪ DAH DUN DUN DAH DOW ♪
OKAY .
♪ DON 'T KNOW WHY I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ DON 'T KNOW WHY I CARE ♪
♪ I REALLY LOVE ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU , DEAR ♪
♪ I WONDER WHY ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU LIKE I DO ♪
♪ IS IT BECAUSE ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU LOVE ME , TOO ? ♪ ♪
CHECK THIS OUT !
♪ KEEP A-KNOCKIN ' , BUT YOU CAN 'T COME IN ♪
♪ KEEP A-KNOCKIN ' , BUT YOU CAN 'T COME — ♪
I HAVE TO GET MY WALLET OUT OF CHRISTINE .
WANT TO COME IN ?
PLEASE .
OKAY .
YOU KNOW , UH ...
I 'VE BEEN THINKING .
MAYBE WE SHOULD APPLY TO THE SAME COLLEGES NEXT YEAR .
REALLY ?
YEAH .
IF WE 'RE ACCEPTED BY THE SAME SCHOOLS ,
WE COULD TAKE IT AS A SIGN OF FATE .
YOU 'D HAVE ME TO HELP YOU THROUGH THE MATH COURSES ,
AND IF ...
ARNIE , WHAT 'S WRONG ?
ARNIE !
OW !
ARNIE ...
WHO DID THIS ?
ARNIE .
DON 'T TOUCH ME , SHITTER !
THIS IS JUST WHAT YOU WANTED !
GET AWAY FROM HER ! GET AWAY FROM HER !
ARNIE , I 'M SORRY .
SORRY ?
YES .
I ...
THAT IS , WE —
IT 'S YOUR FAULT .
IF YOU HADN 'T BEEN SO DAMN SELFISH .
YOU WOULDN 'T LET ME PARK MY OWN CAR IN YOUR PRECIOUS DRIVEWAY .
THIS NEVER WOULD 'VE HAPPENED .
THAT 'S NOT FAIR .
OH , IT 'S FAIR .
CAN 'T WE EVEN TALK ABOUT THIS
LIKE RATIONAL HUMAN BEINGS ?
ONE OF THEM TOOK A SHIT SHIT ON THE DASHBOARD OF MY CAR , MA .
HOW 'S THAT FOR RATIONAL ?
WHY DON 'T WE ...
WE 'LL HELP YOU BUY A NEW CAR .
WELL . THAT 'S WHAT EVERYBODY WANTS , ISN 'T IT ?
WELL , FUCK YOU .
I 'M FIXING UP CHRISTINE .
YOU 'VE BEEN DISRESPECTFUL ONCE TOO OFTEN !
GO BACK THERE AND APOLOGIZE !
TAKE YOUR MITTS OFF ME , MOTHERFUCKER !
[ CHUCKLES ]
I 'M HITTING THE SACK .
WE 'LL MAKE IT BETTER , HUH ?
THEY CAN 'T HURT US ANYMORE .
NOT IF WE WORK TOGETHER .
WE 'LL SHOW THOSE SHITTERS WHAT WE CAN DO .
[ RATTLING ]
OKAY .
SHOW ME .
HEY , CUNNINGHAM !
IS THAT YOU , CUNNINGHAM ?
HEY , YOU AIN 'T MAD , ARE YOU ?
OH , SHIT .
YOU 'RE A DEAD MAN NOW .
AAAHH !
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN , ASSHOLE ?
YOU HEAR ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED TO MOOCHIE ?
YEAH .
ALMOST MAKES YOU FEEL SORRY FOR THE BASTARD , HUH ?
HOW 'S CHRISTINE COMING ?
OH , CHERRY .
I SPENT A SHITLOAD OF MONEY ON HER ,
AND SHE 'S PERFECTO NOW .
THAT 'S FUNNY , YOU KNOW ,
'CAUSE I HEARD SHE WAS TOTALED .
AFTER I CLEANED UP THE BROKEN THE GLASS ,
IT WASN 'T SO BAD .
BET YOU 100 BUCKS ...
IT WAS BUDDY REPPERTON .
MAYBE .
SO WHAT IF YOU FIX IT UP ,
AND HE DOES IT AGAIN ?
HE WON 'T DO IT AGAIN .
WHAT 'S THAT MEAN ?
HEY , MAN , I GOT TO GO .
I HOPE YOU DIDN 'T THINK I 'D BE HANGING AROUND HERE ALL DAY .
THAT 'S YOU , ARNIE , ALWAYS IN DEMAND .
STAY LOOSE .
YOU KNOW IT .
HAPPY THANKSGIVING .
[ BELL RINGS ]
LEAN MACHINE !
THEY LET YOU OUT EARLY ?
YEAH . THAT 'S RIGHT .
ARNOLD CUNNINGHAM ?
I 'M RUDOLPH JUNKINS ,
STATE POLICE DETECTIVE .
I 'M JUST MISSING A STUDY HALL .
I GOTTA GET TO WORK . I DON 'T CARE ABOUT THAT .
I WANT TO ASK ABOUT YOUR CAR .
YOU DO NICE BODYWORK , ARNIE .
I THOUGHT THIS THING WAS TOTALED .
WHO TOLD YOU THAT ?
EVERYBODY .
LOCAL POLICE , YOUR MOM AND DAD , YOUR GIRL .
CUTE GIRL , BY THE WAY .
IT WASN 'T AS BAD AS IT LOOKED .
THE REPORT SAID THEY PUNCHED HOLES IN THE BODY .
DAMN IF I CAN SEE THE FILL .
YOU CAN IF YOU LOOK .
SOMETHING OVER THERE .
AND BACK HERE .
I 'VE BEEN LUCKY WITH PARTS .
I REPLACED THE ENTIRE DOOR ON THIS SIDE .
SEE WHERE THE PAINT DOESN 'T QUITE MATCH ?
NOPE .
IT 'S A HELL OF A JOB . IT 'S A HELL OF A JOB , ARNIE .
THANK YOU VERY MUCH .
[ REVS ENGINE ]
OKAY . SO WHAT DO YOU WANT ?
I LIKE THIS SHADE OF RED , ARNIE .
DIDN 'T THINK THEY MADE THIS ANYMORE .
DO THEY ? THEY STILL MAKE THIS SHADE ?
THEY MUST . I BOUGHT IT .
WHERE ?
BAKER AUTO ON ROUTE FIVE .
YOU GOT THE RECEIPT ?
TOSSED IT OUT .
YOU KNOW , IT 'S FUNNY —
CIGARETTE ?
NO , THANKS .
USUALLY WHEN SOMEBODY TRASHES A CAR ,
WE GET PHOTOGRAPHS .
WAIT , WAIT , WAIT . THEY DIDN 'T REALLY TRASH IT .
THAT 'S NOT WHAT LEIGH SAID .
AS A MATTER OF FACT , SHE WAS SO SHAKEN UP
GIVING ME ALL THE DETAILS , SHE BROKE DOWN CRYING .
I UNDERSTAND , UH ...
ONE OF THE PERPETRATORS
DEFECATED ON THE DASHBOARD .
I 'D HAVE THOUGHT YOU 'D BE MADDER THAN HELL AT THAT ,
AND I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT YOU WOULD HAVE REPORTED THAT .
SHIT WIPES OFF .
MOOCHIE WELLS KIND OF GOT WIPED OFF TOO , DIDN 'T HE ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
YOU DON 'T KNOW ?
NO .
SCOUTS ' HONOR ?
I 'M NOT A SCOUT .
THE KID WAS CUT IN HALF .
THEY HAD TO SCRAPE HIS LEGS UP WITH A SHOVEL .
ISN 'T THAT WHAT YOU DO WITH SHIT ...
SCRAP IT UP WITH A LITTLE SHOVEL ?
DON 'T GET SMART WITH ME .
YOUR GIRLFRIEND IS A LOT MORE CONVINCING THAN YOU ARE .
SHE 'S NOT MY GIRLFRIEND .
AND SINCE WHEN IS IT AGAINST THE LAW
TO FIX UP YOUR OWN CAR WHEN SOMEBODY ELSE BUSTS IT UP ?
SINCE NEVER .
THEN YOU GET OFF MY BACK .
OKAY .
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
HELLO .
HI , LEIGH .
I NEED TO TALK ... I NEED TO SEE YOU .
ARNIE , I CARE ABOUT YOU .
I LOVE YOU , LEIGH .
I THINK WE DESERVE ONE MORE TRY .
DON 'T YOU ?
GIVE ME A FUCKING YES OR NO !
ARNIE , PLEASE DON 'T DO THIS TO ME .
BE STRAIGHT . YOU 'VE HAD IT , RIGHT ?
WELL , FUCK YOU , BITCH !
LEIGH ? LEIGH ?
LEIGH ?
WANT DO TO THE HONORS , MONSIEUR ?
WHOO !
LOVE TO BRING HER ALONG .
SURE .
SHE CAN EARN HER WAY .
BULLSHIT .
LET 'S GET VANDENBERG .
BABY .
♪ I 'LL NEVER BE ♪
♪ YOUR BEAST OF BURDEN ♪
♪ MY BACK IS BROKE ♪
♪ BUT IT 'S NOT HURTIN ' ♪
♪ ALL I WANT ♪
♪ IS FOR YOU TO MAKE LOVE WITH ME ♪
♪ I 'LL NEVER BE ♪
♪ YOUR BEAST OF BURDEN ♪
♪ I 'VE WALKED FOR MILES ♪
♪ MY FEET ARE HURTIN ' ♪
♪ ALL I WANT ... ♪
ASSHOLE !
WATCH THIS .
LET 'S GIVE THIS ASSHOLE SOME OF HIS OWN MEDICINE .
HE 'S BACKING UP , TOO .
SOME SHITHEAD 'S FOLLOWING ME !
I HOPE HE COMES IN HERE !
IS THAT CUNNINGHAM ?
IT CAN 'T BE .
LOOK AT MY CAR .
COME ON , PRICK !
WE 'RE NOT FINISHED !
COME ON !
AHHH !
HELLO , HENRY ?
THIS IS WILL .
LISTEN , CUNNINGHAM GET THERE ?
THE ORDER OKAY ?
GOOD .
HE WAS DRIVING MY CADDIE , WASN 'T HE ?
YEAH . TAKE IT EASY .
OKAY , JACK .
COME ON OUT .
THE RIDE IS OVER .
IF I 'M GONNA HAVE TO COME IN AND GET YOU ,
I 'M GOING TO GET YOU .
WHY DON 'T YOU DO US BOTH A FAVOR ?
COME ON OUT .
OUCH !
GEEZ .
♪ I GOT A GIRL NAMED BONY MARONIE ♪
♪ SHE 'S AS SKINNY AS A STICK OF MACARONI ♪
♪ OUGHT TO SEE HER ROCK AND ROLL ♪
♪ WITH HER BLUE JEANS ON ♪
♪ NOT VERY FAT JUST SKIN AND BONES ♪
♪ I LOVE HER ♪
♪ SHE LOVES ME ♪
♪ OH , HOW HAPPY NOW ♪
♪ WE CAN BE ♪
♪ MAKING LOVE UNDERNEATH THE APPLE TREE ♪
♪ WELL , I TOLD HER MAMA AND HER PAPA , TOO ♪ ♪
WHAT 'S GOING ON ?
YOU TELL ME . WHERE WERE YOU LAST NIGHT ?
HOME . WHY ? WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO MY CAR ?
YOU DIDN 'T GO OUT ?
OF COURSE I WENT OUT .
I GOT DARNELL 'S CAR OUT FRONT WITH A LOAD OF PARTS .
YOU WANT THE RECEIPT ?
YEAH .
HOW COME YOU 'RE SHOWING UP JUST NOW ?
WHY DIDN 'T YOU UNLOAD LAST NIGHT ?
'CAUSE I WAS TIRED , THAT 'S WHY .
IF YOU DON 'T BELIEVE ME , YOU CAN ASK MY MOTHER .
WHY DO YOU KEEP BUTTING INTO MY LIFE ?
BECAUSE WE FOUND YOUR BOSS , WILL DARNELL , DEAD
IN YOUR FRONT SEAT ,
WITH A SHOTGUN BY HIS SIDE .
WHY ?
I WAS HOPING YOU COULD ANSWER THAT .
SOMEBODY SAW YOUR CAR
CRUISING BEHIND BUDDY REPPERTON LAST NIGHT .
HE 'S DEAD , TOO .
SO ARE DON VANDENBERG AND RICHARD CHALLONY .
GUESS NOBODY WILL BE TRASHING YOUR CAR ANYMORE .
WELL , ALL I KNOW —
ALL I KNOW IS I GOT A CADILLAC OUT FRONT FULL OF PARTS —
WE 'LL TAKE CARE OF THE CADDIE .
I DON 'T WANT YOU TOUCHING IT .
HONEST , MR. JUNKINS ,
I DON 'T KNOW WHAT 'S GOING ON .
I SWEAR I DON 'T .
MAY I PLEASE SPEAK TO DENNIS ?
IT 'S A GIRL .
HELLO .
HEY , LEIGH .
HAPPY NEW YEAR .
CAN I COME OVER THERE ?
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU .
WHAT , ABOUT ARNIE ?
ABOUT CHRISTINE .
OKAY .
YOU FIRST .
I 'M AFRAID FOR ARNIE .
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED TO TALK ABOUT CHRISTINE .
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT CAR ?
THE GUY WHO OWNED THE CAR BEFORE ARNIE ...
YEAH ?
HIS DAUGHTER CHOKED TO DEATH IN CHRISTINE .
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT ?
LeBAY 'S BROTHER SOLD ARNIE THE CAR .
THE GUY 'S A JERK . HE TOLD ME .
I THINK I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE NEXT OR SOMETHING .
OH , COME ON , LEIGH .
ARNIE WOULD NEVER DO THAT .
NOT IN A MILLION YEARS , OKAY ?
I DON 'T THINK HE 'S ARNIE , DENNIS .
IT 'S THAT CAR .
I SWEAR IT 'S THE CAR .
MAYBE .
I 'M GOING TO ARNIE 'S TONIGHT FOR NEW YEAR 'S —
DENNIS , I WOULDN 'T .
IT 'S OKAY .
HIS FOLKS WILL BE THERE .
I JUST FIGURE THAT MAYBE IF I GET HIM ALONE ,
MAYBE HE 'LL TALK TO ME .
WHAT IF HE DOESN 'T ?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
I DON 'T KNOW . WHAT IF ...
WHAT IF THAT CAR DOESN 'T LET HIM ?
THEN WE DESTROY IT .
[ HORN HONKS ]
♪ ALL THE WAY DOWN THERE ♪
♪ COME ON , LET 'S GO , LITTLE DARLING ♪
♪ LET 'S GO , LET 'S GO ♪
HA HA HA !
HEY , MY MAN , YOU 'RE REALLY OPERATING THOSE BABIES .
YEAH , I MANAGE .
YOU GOT THE OLD RUST BUCKET ?
YOU WANNA WATCH WHAT YOU CALL MY CAR .
SHE 'S REAL SENSITIVE .
IS SHE ?
SORRY , CHRISTINE .
GOOD BOY .
LET 'S MOTIVATE .
WELL , HAVE A BEER . DON 'T BE SHY .
MY CAR 'S YOUR CAR .
A TOAST TO ...
DEATH !
TO THE SHITTERS OF THE WORLD IN 1979 .
COME ON , ARNIE . I CAN 'T DRINK TO THAT .
WHAT CAN YOU DRINK TO ?
WHAT ABOUT US ? OUR FRIENDSHIP ?
FRIENDSHIP .
ALL RIGHT . THAT 'S REAL GOOD .
HEY , DENNIS .
TA-DA !
COME OFF IT .
I WANT YOU TO SEE THIS . I WANT YOU TO SEE THIS .
THIS IS A GREAT ALIGNMENT . YOU JUST DON 'T SEE THIS ANY ...
DON 'T BE SCARED .
I 'M SCARED FOR YOU , MAN . FOR WHAT 'S HAPPENED TO YOU .
IT 'S THIS FUCKING CAR .
I KNOW YOU 'RE JEALOUS .
BUT WE 'LL BE FRIENDS AS LONG AS YOU STICK WITH ME .
AND YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS TO SHITTERS WHO DON 'T .
NO .
WHAT DOES HAPPEN ?
LET 'S NOT KID EACH OTHER , DENNIS .
WHO ARE THE SHITTERS ?
ALL OF THEM .
ARNIE ...
LEIGH 'S ON YOUR SIDE .
OH , YEAH ?
SHE CARES A LOT ABOUT YOU .
SHE DOES .
YEAH .
DON 'T YOU LIKE THIS BEER ? THOUGHT YOU LIKED BEER .
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I JUST SAID ?
LET ME TELL YOU A LITTLE SOMETHING ABOUT LOVE , DENNIS .
IT HAS VORACIOUS APPETITE .
IT EATS EVERYTHING —
FRIENDSHIP ,
FAMILY .
IT KILLS ME HOW MUCH IT EATS .
BUT I 'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING ELSE .
YOU FEED IT RIGHT , AND IT CAN BE A BEAUTIFUL THING ,
AND THAT 'S WHAT WE HAVE .
WHEN SOMEONE BELIEVES IN YOU ,
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING . ANY FUCKING THING IN THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE .
AND WHEN YOU BELIEVE IN THAT SOMEONE , THEN WATCH OUT , WORLD ,
'CAUSE NOBODY CAN STOP YOU . NOBODY , EVER .
YOU FEEL THIS WAY ABOUT LEIGH ?
WHAT ? FUCK , NO !
I 'M TALKING ABOUT CHRISTINE .
NO SHITTER EVER CAME BETWEEN ME AND CHRISTINE .
NOW WATCH THIS !
[ HORN BLARES ]
CHICKENSHIT !
OH , MAN , THERE IS NOTHING FINER
THAN BEING BEHIND THE WHEEL OF YOUR OWN CAR .
EXCEPT MAYBE FOR PUSSY .
HEY .
IT 'S KIND OF SPOOKY IN HERE , HUH ?
LOOKS LIKE THEY CLEANED OUT THE PLACE .
THAT 'S WHERE HE USED TO KEEP IT .
DOWN THERE .
YEAH .
WE BETTER GET STARTED .
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
YEAH !
WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
LET 'S TRY IT .
CHRISTINE 'S GOTTA COME THROUGH THE DOOR .
YOU BETTER GET IN THE OFFICE AND STAY OUT OF SIGHT .
ONCE SHE GETS INSIDE , HIT THE BUTTON AND BRING THE DOOR DOWN .
THEN WE 'LL HAVE HER TRAPPED .
WHAT IF HE DOESN 'T COME ?
CHRISTINE WILL .
LOOK , YOU BETTER GET IN THE OFFICE .
KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN .
WHEN YOU HEAR ME START THIS THING UP ,
THAT 'S WHEN YOU REACH OUT AND HIT THE BUTTON .
LEIGH !
AHH !
LEIGH , DON 'T MOVE . STAY WHERE YOU ARE .
YOU SHITTERS !
AHHH !
AHHHH !
ARNIE 'S DEAD .
♪ I 'LL FOREVER LOVE YOU ♪
♪ THE REST OF MY DAYS ... ♪
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
LEIGH !
YOU OKAY ?
I THINK SO .
NO !
OH !
♪ AH , AH , AH , AH , OH , BABY ♪
♪ AH , AH , AH , AH ♪
♪ ROCK AND ROLL IS HERE TO STAY ♪
♪ IT WILL NEVER DIE ♪
♪ IT 'S OKAY TO FEEL THAT WAY ♪
♪ THOUGH I DON 'T KNOW WHY ♪
♪ WE DON 'T CARE WHAT PEOPLE SAY ♪
♪ ROCK AND ROLL IS HERE TO STAY ♪
♪ ROCK AND ROLL WILL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ OUR TICKET TO THE END ... ♪
I WOULDN 'T FEEL SO BAD IF I WERE YOU .
YOU TWO ARE HEROES .
YEAH . A REAL HERO COULD HAVE SAVED ARNIE .
WE DIDN 'T DO SO HOT .
SOME THINGS CAN 'T BE HELPED .
SOME PEOPLE , TOO .
YEAH .
♪ I LOVE YOU SO ♪
♪ AND I 'LL NEVER LET YOU GO ♪
♪ COME ON , BABY ... ♪
GOD , I HATE ROCK AND ROLL .
♪ NOW , ON THE DAY I WAS BORN ♪
♪ THE NURSES ALL GATHERED ' ROUND ♪
♪ AND THEY GAZED IN WIDE WONDER ♪
♪ AT THE JOY THEY HAD FOUND ♪
♪ THE HEAD NURSE SPOKE UP ♪
♪ SAID , " LEAVE THIS ONE ALONE " ♪
♪ SHE COULD TELL RIGHT AWAY ♪
♪ THAT I WAS BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ B-B-B-B-B-BAD ♪
♪ I BROKE 1,000 HEARTS ♪
♪ BEFORE I MET YOU ♪
♪ I 'LL BREAK 1,000 MORE , BABY ♪
♪ BEFORE I AM THROUGH ♪
♪ I WANT TO BE YOURS , PRETTY BABY ♪
♪ YOURS , AND YOURS ALONE ♪
♪ I 'M HERE TO TELL YOU , HONEY ♪
♪ THAT I 'M BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ B-B-B-B-B-BAD ♪
♪ I MAKE A RICH WOMAN BEG ♪
♪ AND I MAKE A GOOD WOMAN STEAL ♪
♪ I MAKE AN OLD WOMAN BLUSH ♪
♪ AND I MAKE A YOUNG GIRL SQUEAL ♪
♪ I WANT TO BE YOURS , PRETTY BABY ♪
♪ YOURS AND YOURS ALONE ♪
♪ I 'M HERE TO TELL YOU , HONEY ♪
♪ THAT I 'M BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ B-B-B-B-B-BAD ♪
♪ BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ AND WHEN I WALK THE STREETS ♪
♪ KINGS AND QUEENS STEP ASIDE ♪
♪ EVERY WOMAN I MEET ♪
♪ THEY ALL STAY SATISFIED ♪
♪ I WANT TO TELL YOU , PRETTY BABY ♪
♪ WHAT I SEE , I MAKE MY OWN ♪
♪ AND LET ME TELL YOU , HONEY ♪
♪ THAT I 'M BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ BAD TO THE BONE ♪
♪ B-B-B-B-B-BAD ♪
♪ BAD TO THE BONE ♪ ♪